<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><MD_Metadata xmlns:gts="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gts" xmlns:gco="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gco" xmlns:xalan="http://xml.apache.org/xalan" xmlns:srv="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/srv" xmlns:gmx="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gmx" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml" xmlns="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gmd">
    <characterSet>
        <MD_CharacterSetCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#MD_CharacterSetCode" codeListValue="utf8" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">utf8</MD_CharacterSetCode>
    </characterSet>
    <hierarchyLevel>
        <MD_ScopeCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#MD_ScopeCode" codeListValue="dataset" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">dataset</MD_ScopeCode>
    </hierarchyLevel>
    <hierarchyLevelName>
        <gco:CharacterString>dataset</gco:CharacterString>
    </hierarchyLevelName>
    <contact gco:nilReason="missing"/>
    <dateStamp gco:nilReason="missing"/>
    <metadataStandardName>
        <gco:CharacterString>ISO 19139 Geographic Information - Metadata - Implementation Specification</gco:CharacterString>
    </metadataStandardName>
    <metadataStandardVersion>
        <gco:CharacterString>2007</gco:CharacterString>
    </metadataStandardVersion>
    <identificationInfo>
        <MD_DataIdentification>
            <citation gco:nilReason="missing"/>
            <abstract>
                <gco:CharacterString>Named Waterbody is a 1:24,000-scale, polygon and line feature-based layer that includes all named waterbodies depicted on the U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) 7.5 minute topographic quadrangle maps for the State of Connecticut. This layer only includes features located in Connecticut. Named Waterbody features include water, dams, flow connectors, aqueducts, canals, ditches, shorelines, and islands. The layer does not include the marsh areas, tidal flats, rocks, shoals, or channels typically shown on USGS 7.5 minute topographic quadrangle maps. However, the layer includes linear (flow) connector features that fill in gaps between river and stream features where water passes through marshes or underground through pipelines and tunnels. Note that connectors represent general pathways and do not represent the exact location or orientation of actual underground pipelines, tunnels, aqueducts, etc. The Named Waterbody layer is comprised of polygon and line features. Polygon features represent areas of water for rivers, streams, brooks, reservoirs, lakes, ponds, bays, coves, and harbors. Polygon features also depict related information such as dams and islands. Line features represent single-line rivers and streams, flow connectors, aqueducts, canals, and ditches. Line features also enclose all polygon features in the form of shorelines, dams, and closure lines separating adjacent water features. The Named Waterbody layer is based on information from USGS topographic quadrangle maps published between 1969 and 1984 so it does not depict conditions at any one particular point in time. Also, the layer does not reflect recent changes with the course of streams or location of shorelines impacted by natural events or changes in development since the time the USGS 7.5 minute topographic quadrangle maps were published. Attribute information is comprised of codes to identify waterbody features by type, cartographically represent (symbolize) waterbody features on a map, select waterbodies appropriate to display at different map scales, identify individual waterbodies on a map by name, and describe waterbody feature area and length. The names assigned to individual waterbodies are based on information published on the USGS 7.5 minute topographic quadrangle maps or other state and local maps. The Named Waterbody layer does not include bathymetric, stream gradient, water flow, water quality, or biological habitat information. Derived from the Hydrography layer, the Named Waterbody layer was originally published in 1999. The 2005 edition includes the same water features published in 1999, however some attribute information has been slightly modified and made easier to use. Also, the 2005 edition corrects previously undetected attribute coding errors and includes the flow connector features. Connecticut Named Waterbody Polygon includes the polygon features of a layer named Named Waterbody. Named Waterbody is a 1:24,000-scale, polygon and line feature-based layer that includes all named waterbodies depicted on the U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) 7.5 minute topographic quadrangle maps for the State of Connecticut. This layer only includes features located in Connecticut. Named Waterbody features include water, dams, flow connectors, aqueducts, canals, ditches, shorelines, and islands. The layer does not include the marsh areas, tidal flats, rocks, shoals, or channels typically shown on USGS 7.5 minute topographic quadrangle maps. However, the layer includes linear (flow) connector features that fill in gaps between river and stream features where water passes through marshes or underground through pipelines and tunnels. Note that connectors represent general pathways and do not represent the exact location or orientation of actual underground pipelines, tunnels, aqueducts, etc. The Named Waterbody layer is comprised of polygon and line features. Polygon features represent areas of water for rivers, streams, brooks, reservoirs, lakes, ponds, bays, coves, and harbors. Polygon features also depict related information such as dams and islands. Line features represent single-line rivers and streams, flow connectors, aqueducts, canals, and ditches. Line features also enclose all polygon features in the form of shorelines, dams, and closure lines separating adjacent water features. The Named Waterbody layer is based on information from USGS topographic quadrangle maps published between 1969 and 1984 so it does not depict conditions at any one particular point in time. Also, the layer does not reflect recent changes with the course of streams or location of shorelines impacted by natural events or changes in development since the time the USGS 7.5 minute topographic quadrangle maps were published. Attribute information is comprised of codes to identify waterbody features by type, cartographically represent (symbolize) waterbody features on a map, select waterbodies appropriate to display at different map scales, identify individual waterbodies on a map by name, and describe waterbody feature area and length. The names assigned to individual waterbodies are based on information published on the USGS 7.5 minute topographic quadrangle maps or other state and local maps. The Named Waterbody layer does not include bathymetric, stream gradient, water flow, water quality, or biological habitat information. Derived from the Hydrography layer, the Named Waterbody layer was originally published in 1999. The 2005 edition includes the same water features published in 1999, however some attribute information has been slightly modified and made easier to use. Also, the 2005 edition corrects previously undetected attribute coding errors and includes the flow connector features.</gco:CharacterString>
            </abstract>
            <purpose>
                <gco:CharacterString>Named Waterbody Set: Connecticut Named Waterbody Line includes the line features of a layer named Named Waterbody Line and the polygon features of a layer named Named Waterbody Poly. </gco:CharacterString>
            </purpose>
            <credit>
                <gco:CharacterString>CTDEEP</gco:CharacterString>
            </credit>
            <descriptiveKeywords>
                <MD_Keywords>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>Waterbody</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>Hydrography</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>digital line graph</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>DLG</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>large scale</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>hydrography</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>river</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>stream</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>lake</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>pond</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>water</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>waterbody</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>base map</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>CT</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>open</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>data</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>open data</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>named</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>set</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>DEEP</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                    <keyword>
                        <gco:CharacterString>CTDEEP</gco:CharacterString>
                    </keyword>
                </MD_Keywords>
            </descriptiveKeywords>
            <resourceConstraints>
                <MD_Constraints>
                    <useLimitation>
                        <gco:CharacterString>CC0</gco:CharacterString>
                    </useLimitation>
                </MD_Constraints>
            </resourceConstraints>
            <language gco:nilReason="missing"/>
            <characterSet>
                <MD_CharacterSetCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#MD_CharacterSetCode" codeListValue="utf8" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">utf8</MD_CharacterSetCode>
            </characterSet>
        </MD_DataIdentification>
    </identificationInfo>
</MD_Metadata>
